

□ (+1) 647-708-5763 | salimansour@gmail.com | slimnsour.me | slimnsour.me

## Summary\_

Software Engineering student graduating from the University of Toronto in April 2020. Professional experience specializing in software design, testing, and implementation. Huge video game enthusiast, aiming to be a indispensable asset to a talented development team in the industry.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Centre for Addiction and Mental Health**

NEUROIMAGING RESEARCH ANALYST

May 2019 - August 2019

- Implemented imaging preprocessing pipelines for neuroscience research and used them to efficiently prepare data for 6 unique studies totalling over 500 subjects.
- Redesigned large projects in the neuroscience community including dmriprep and Nipype, and created tractography pipeline tractify to decrease generation time from an hour to 15 minutes.

#### Geosoft Inc.

**AUTOMATED TEST ENGINEER** 

January 2018 - August 2018

- Tested main product Oasis montaj through Ranorex by managing over 1000 tests for each release and reporting results, decreasing the average failure rate for each build by 30%.
- · Presented results in weekly meetings, communicating with coworkers in other departments to boost understanding of automated testing.

### Education

### **University of Toronto**

HBSc Specialist in Software Engineering, GPA 3.7/4.0

September 2016 - April 2020

- Achieved UofT Scholars Entrance Award for being among the top 700 students admitted.
- Awarded Dean's List every year for maintaining a high GPA.

## **Projects**

#### **Balloonatics**

GAME DEVELOPMENT

September 2019 - present

Developing an action platformer, solving experimental programming challenges including seamless level looping and practicing iterative improvement of game feel and user experience.

#### **Ray Tracer**

COMPUTER GRAPHICS, UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

September 2019 - December 2019

Built a ray tracer in C, combining linear algebra and programming concepts to implement advanced features including multithreading, depth
of field, and refraction.

#### **Tractify**

NEUROIMAGING PREPROCESSING PIPELINE

May 2019 - August 2019

Designed and built an efficient tractography generation pipeline using software design principles to greatly decrease runtime, and containerized
it using Docker for accessibility and reproducibility.

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Game Dev Club**

**Executive**January 2018 - present

 Coordinating with a team to gather resources and plan projects to showcase in weekly meetings, explaining the logic behind popular game mechanics to guide beginners.

# Languages\_

**Programming** C, Python, C#, C++, Java, R, HTML, SQL, Bash

**Testing** Ranorex, JUnit, Selenium **Game Development** Unity, GameMaker:Studio